A Guide to the papers of Thomas C. Fichandler (1915-1997), Founding Executive Diector of the Arena Stage, 1950-2000
George Mason University Libraries
Special Collections and Archives, George Mason University
Thomas C. Fichanlder papers 1950-1997
Special Collections and Archives, George Mason University
Arena0010
35 boxes, 16 cubic feet (24 linear feet)
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
This collection was donated by the Arena Stage in 2000
Biographical Information
Arena Stage was an early leader in the resident theater movement. One of the first not-for-profit theaters in the United States as well as a pioneer of the regional theater movement the Arena Stage was the first regional theater to transfer a production to Broadway, the first invited by the U.S. State Department to tour behind the Iron Curtain and the first to receive a Tony Award. Co-founded in 1950 by Edward Mangum a teacher from the George Washington University, and Zelda Fichandler one of his students, Arena Stage was opened in Washington D.C. to fill the void left by the closing of the National Theater in 1948. Deriving it's name from the idea of "theater in the round," Arena Stage became one of the first resident theaters in the United States, beginning with a company of only eight actors. Today, Arena performs to over 250,000 patrons during a September to June season and employs nearly 200 theater professionals and craftpersons, who are responsible for all the costumes and scenery seen on stage. Many now- famous actors took part in Arena Stage productions during the early part of their careers. Some of them include Robert Prosky, Morgan Freeman, Dianne Weist, James Earl Jones, Kevin Kline, Christopher Guest, Yeardly Smith and Samuel L. Jackson. Donated to George Mason University in fall of 2000, the Arena Stage Collection contains materials spanning the theater's 50 year history including production notebooks, photographs, playbills, scrapbooks, scripts and handwritten correspondence and other production materials.
Scope and Content
containes correspondence, memos, reports and other papers generated by Thomas C. Fichandler
Arrangement
by subject
Contents List
- Arena Stage: Thomas C. Fichandler files
  - Investment Committee files 1983, Folder 1 (Box Box 1)
  - Council of the District of Columbia: Notice of Public hearing, Folder 2 (Box Box 1)
  - David L. Kreeger 1977, Folder 3 (Box Box 1)
  - C and P Telephone letter to Thomas C. Fichandler 11/18/82, Folder 4 (Box Box 1)
  - Israel Festival 1983, Folder 5 (Box box 1)
  - Investment CT, Bill Stewart 1988 - 1990, Folder 7 (Box Box 1)
  - Historic Site Application 1980, Folder 8 (Box Box 1)
  - League of Resident Theatres by-laws, Folder 9 (Box Box 1)
  - Humanities Program, Folder 10 (Box Box 1)
  - Historic site application: letters of support 1980, Folder 11 (Box Box 1)
  - Historic Site: letters of support, Folder 12 (Box Box 1)
  - Historic Site: letters of support, Folder 13 (Box Box 1)
  - Historic Site: Letters of Support, Folder 14 (Box Box 1)
    Letters from the U.S. Department of the Interior
  - Historic Site: letters of support, Folder 15 (Box Box 1)
    Letters from the Commission on the Arts and Humanities
  - Historic Site: Letters of support, Folder 16 (Box Box 1)
  - Historic Site: application 1980, Folder 17 (Box Box 1)
    application to the National Capitals Planning Commission's Joint Committee on Application for the Designation of Historic Landmarks
  - Long Rnage Planning, Folder 18 (Box Box 1)
  - League of Washington Theatres, Folder 19 (Box Box 1)
  - architectural plans/designs, Loose leaf plans (Box Box 2)
  - New Play Agreement: American Conservatory Theatre, Folder 1 (Box Box 3)
  - Literary Rights Inquiries 1980 - 1982, Folder 2 (Box Box 3)
  - Producation contracts/agreements (Domestic), Folder 3 (Box Box 3)
  - Production contracts/agreements (foreign), Folder 4 (Box Box 3)
  - Living Stage Committee, Folder 5 (Box Box 3)
  - Living Stage Committee 1989 - 1990, Folder 6 (Box Box 3)
  - Evaluative Survey and Renovation Analysis, Folder 7 (Box Box 3)
  - Living Stage building, Folder 8 (Box Box 3)
  - Management Consultants, Folder 9 (Box Box 3)
  - Metro, Folder 10 (Box Box 3)
  - Major Arts Org. government funding, Folder 11 (Box Box 3)
  - Workshop Particpation, Folder 1 (Box Box 4)
  - Sign up workshop: food and count/participation, Folder 2 (Box Box 4)
  - Weekend Agenda, Folder 3 (Box Box 4)
  - Mission Statement January 1984 (1), Folder 4 (Box Box 4)
  - Mission Statement January 1984 (2), Folder 5 (Box Box 4)
  - Managing Directors Search 1983-1985, Folder 6 (Box Box 4)
  - Marketing Committee, Folder 7 (Box Box 4)
  - Budget 1988 (1), Folder 8 (Box Box 4)
  - Budget 1988 (2), Folder 9 (Box Box 4)
  - Board Retreat 1985, Folder 10 (Box Box 4)
  - Retreat 1983 (Wye Plantation), Folder 11 (Box box 4)
  - Rubenstein's Barn on the Chaptank, Folder 12 (Box Box 4)
  - Fall Conference for Future Trustee mailing, Folder 13 (Box Box 4)
  - Board Meeting Agenda 9/29/85, Folder 14 (Box Box 4)
  - Wye Plantation - KLC, Folder 15 (Box Box 4)
  - Budget 1986-1987(1), Folder 1 (Box Box 5)
  - budget 1986-1987 (2), Folder 2 (Box box 5)
  - Budget 1985-1986 (1), Folder 3 (Box Box 5)
  - Budget 1985-1986, Folder 4 (Box Box 5)
  - Budget Committee 1979-1984, Folder 5 (Box Box 5)
  - National Theatre Center, Folder 6 (Box Box 5)
  - Fall Conference for Future Agenda - programing retreat 1985 Wye Plantation, Folder 7 (Box box 5)
  - Washington Drama Society Inc.: Management letter 6/30/86, Folder 8 (Box Box 5)
  - Budget 1981-1986, Folder 9 (Box Box 5)
  - Building and Property, Folder 10 (Box Box 5)
  - Budget 1988-1989: 7/19/88 update, Folder 11 (Box Box 5)
  - D.C. income tax exemption, Folder 1 (Box Box 6)
  - Arena Stage Taxes, Folder 2 (Box Box 6)
  - Tax Exemptions: Kreeger Land, Folder 3 (Box Box 6)
  - Arena Stage tax report and exemptions, Folder 4 (Box Box 6)
  - Tax Report and Exemptions, Folder 5 (Box Box 6)
  - analysis of successful organizations, Folder 6 (Box box 6)
  - William Stewart" General Correspondence July ,1988, Folder 7 (Box Box 6)
  - Willaim Stewart: General Correspondence August, 1988, Folder 8 (Box Box 6)
  - William Stewart: General Correspondence September, 1988, Folder 9 (Box Box 6)
  - William Stewart: General Correspondence October 1988, Folder 10 (Box Box 6)
  - William Stewart: General Correspondence November 1988, Folder 11 (Box Box 6)
  - Payment: Edward M. Crough, Contractor, Folder 12 (Box Box 6)
  - Payment: Edward M. Crough, Contractor, Folder 13 (Box Box 6)
  - Payment: Edward M. Crough, Contractor, Folder 14 (Box Box 6)
  - Payment: Edward M. Crough, Contractor, Folder 15 (Box Box 6)
  - Paymeny: Edward M. Crough, Contractor, Folder 16 (Box Box 6)
  - Payment: Edward M. Crough, Contractor, Folder 17 (Box Box 6)
  - William Stewart: General Correspondence April 1989, Folder 18 (Box Box 6)
  - William Stewart: General Correspondence March 1989, Folder 19 (Box Box 6)
  - William Stewart: Correspondence January 1989, Folder 20 (Box Box 6)
  - William Stewart: Correspondence May 1989, Folder 21 (Box Box 6)
  - William Stewart: Correspondence June 1989, Folder 22 (Box box 6)
  - William Stewart: Correspondence August 1989, Folder 23 (Box Box 6)
  - William Stewart: Correspondence July1989, Folder 24 (Box Box 6)
  - William Stewart: Correspondence September 1989, Folder 25 (Box Box 6)
  - Willaim Stewart: Correspondence December 1988, Folder 26 (Box Box 6)
  - Payments: Edward M. Crough, Folder 27 (Box Box 6)
  - Payment: Edward M. Crough, Contractor, Folder 28 (Box Box 6)
  - Payment: Edward M. Crough, Contractor, Folder 29 (Box Box 6)
  - Payment: Edward M. Crough, Contractor, Folder 30 (Box Box 6)
  - Payment: Edward M. Crough, Contractor, Folder 31 (Box Box 6)
  - Payment. Edward M. Crough, Contractor, Folder 32 (Box Box 6)
  - Arena Stage Memos on Russia, Folder 1 (Box Box 7)
  - Memos on Russia Tour, Folder 2 (Box Box 7)
  - United States Information Agency info on USSR, Folder 3 (Box Box 7)
  - USSR - Protocol, Folder 4 (Box Box 7)
  - Arena Stage USSR Tour - June 1989, Folder 5 (Box Box 7)
  - USSR Tour Finance, Folder 6 (Box Box 7)
  - Harry Weese and Associates, concrete contract, Folder 7 (Box Box 7)
  - Summer Workshop: Colorado 1985, Folder 8 (Box Box 7)
  - Theatre Communications Group 1984-1985, Folder 9 (Box Box 7)
  - Theatre Institute at Storm king, Folder 10 (Box Box 7)
  - Arena Stage: finance and ticket pricing committee meetings, Folder 11 (Box Box 7)
  - USSR Tour, State Department Materials, Folder 12 (Box Box 7)
  - Questions and general info on USSR Tour, Folder 13 (Box Box 7)
  - Personnel Manifest: USSR tour, Folder 14 (Box Box 7)
  - Actors Equity Association info: Tour of USSR, Folder 15 (Box Box 7)
  - Embassy of USA at Moscow, Folder 16 (Box Box 7)
  - USSR tour general info, Folder 17 (Box Box 7)
  - Israel Festival 1987, Folder 18 (Box Box 7)
  - Ticket Price Sub-Committee, Folder 19 (Box Box 7)
  - Gift of Land: White Sands, Folder 20 (Box Box 7)
  - Turn Around Meetings (I-V), Folder 21 (Box Box 7)
  - Articals on USSR tour, Folder 22 (Box Box 7)
  - Board Meeting 3/17/87, Folder 1 (Box Box 8)
  - Board Meeting 9/22/87, Folder 2 (Box Box 8)
  - Recommended Nominations for Officers and Memos, Folder 3 (Box Box 8)
  - General board Documents: board meeting memorandum and minutes, Folder 4 (Box Box 8)
  - Board Correspondence, Folder 5 (Box Box 8)
  - Board Correspondence, Folder 6 (Box Box 8)
  - Responsibilities of the Board of Trustees, Folder 7 (Box Box 8)
  - General Board Documents: budget report to Board of Trustees, Annual Giving report, Folder 8 (Box Box 8)
  - Board of Trustees Committee Assignments (revised), Folder 9 (Box Box 8)
  - Board Leadership, Folder 10 (Box Box 8)
  - Board of Trustees Committee Assignments, Folder 11 (Box Box 8)
  - Harry Weese file, Folder 12 (Box Box 8)
  - Harry Weese files, Folder 13 (Box Box 8)
  - Harry Weese file, Folder 14 (Box Box 8)
  - Harry Weese file, Folder 15 (Box Box 8)
  - Kreeger Theater: cost per square foot and volume, Folder 16 (Box Box 8)
  - Wye Plantation Information, Folder 17 (Box Box 8)
  - Sir Oliver and Lady Wright Farewell event, Folder 18 (Box Box 8)
  - Harry Weese file 1969-1970, Folder 19 (Box Box 8)
  - Bill Stewart - Board Correspondence, Folder 1 (Box Box 9)
  - Bill Stewart - Board Correspondence, Folder 2 (Box Box 9)
  - General Board Information, Folder 3 (Box Box 9)
  - Ad Hoc Board Structures 1986, Folder 4 (Box Box 9)
  - Ad Hoc Board Structures 1985, Folder 5 (Box Box 9)
  - Ad Hoc Board Structures 1984, Folder 6 (Box Box 9)
  - Ad Hoc Board Structures / Information for Members of the Board of Trustees, Folder 7 (Box Box 9)
  - Annual Board Meeting 6/17/88, Folder 8 (Box Box 9)
  - Full Board Meeting 3-29-88, Folder 9 (Box Box 9)
  - Board Meeting June 16, 1987, Folder 10 (Box Box 9)
  - Full Board Meeting 1/26/88, Folder 11 (Box Box 9)
  - Board of Trustees directory 1988 - 1989, Folder 12 (Box Box 9)
  - Full Board Meeting / Budget / Trustees 3/17/87, Folder 13 (Box Box 9)
  - Arena Stage Letterhead Memos, Folder 14 (Box Box 9)
  - Arena Stage Evaluation and Nomination Committee, Folder 15 (Box Box 9)
  - Alder and Alder / Board participation Program, Folder 16 (Box Box 9)
  - Full Board Meeting 9-27-88, Folder 17 (Box Box 9)
  - Trustee Information Book 1988 - 1989
  - Fall Conference for the Future (1983): analysis of financial trends and future needs, Folder 1 (Box Box 10)
  - Macneille Lunch honoring Marcus Cohn, Folder 2 (Box Box 10)
  - Board of Trustees meeting 1/24/89, Folder 3 (Box Box 10)
  - Annual Board Meeting 6/6/89, Folder 4 (Box Box 10)
  - Board Orientation 10/28/85, Folder 5 (Box Box 10)
  - Rasing minimum board requierments meetiing :minutes, Folder 6 (Box Box 10)
  - Financial Statment: end of Fiscal Year 1989, Folder 7 (Box Box 10)
  - Board of Trustees budget meeting 3/28/89, Folder 8 (Box Box 10)
  - Roles and Responsibilities for the Board of Trustees (November 1984), Folder 9 (Box Box 10)
  - Ad hoc Board Direction Commitee, Folder 10 (Box Box 10)
  - Newspaper Articals on Arena Stage, Folder 11 (Box Box 10)
  - budget for retreat, folder 12 (Box Box 10)
  - Board retreat memos 1983, Folder 13 (Box Box 10)
  - Board Retreat 1983, Folder 14 (Box Box 10)
  - Board retreat, September1981, Folder 15 (Box Box 10)
  - Wye Plantation retreat 1981, Folder 16 (Box Box 10)
  - Board retreat, Airlie, VA September 1977, Folder 17 (Box Box 10)
  - William Stewart Correspondence, June 1987, Folder 1 (Box Box 11)
  - William Stewart Correspondence, April 1987, Folder 2 (Box Box 11)
  - William Stewart Correspondence, May 1987, Folder 3 (Box Box 11)
  - William Stewart Correspondence, February 1987, Folder 4 (Box Box 11)
  - William Stewart Correspondence, March 1987, Folder 5 (Box Box 11)
  - William Stewart Correspondence, January 1987, Folder 6 (Box Box 11)
  - William Stewart Correspondence, December 1986, Folder 7 (Box Box 11)
  - William Stewart Correspondence, April 1986, Folder 8 (Box Box 11)
  - Board Responsibility1985 - 1986, Folder 9 (Box Box 11)
  - Ad Hoc Board Responsibility 1986 - 1987, Folder 10 (Box Box 11)
  - Board orientation material, Folder 11 (Box Box 11)
  - William Stewart Correspondence, October 1986, Folder 12 (Box Box 11)
  - William Stewart Correspondence, November 1986, Folder 13 (Box Box 11)
  - William Stewart Correspondence, February/March 1986, Folder 14 (Box Box 11)
  - William Stewart Correspondence, January 1986, Folder 15 (Box Box 11)
  - Board Reorganization, 1983 - 1984, Folder 16 (Box Box 11)
  - Ad Hoc Board Responsibility 1985, Folder 17 (Box Box 11)
  - Ad Hoc Board Responsibility 1984, Folder 18 (Box Box 11)
  - William Stewart Correspondence, May 1986, Folder 19 (Box Box 11)
  - William Stewart Correspondence, June 1986, Folder 20 (Box Box 11)
  - William Stewart Correspondence, July 1986 (Box Box 21)
  - William Stewart Correspondence, August 1986, Folder 22 (Box Box 11)
  - William Stewart Correspondence, September 1986, Folder 23 (Box Box 11)
  - Equity/ League of Resident Theater negotiations, Folder 1 (Box Box 12)
  - League of Resident Theatres membership, Folder 2 (Box Box 12)
  - Theatres listings / LORT managers / weekly box office gross, Folder 4 (Box Box 12)
  - Equity / LORT negotiations, Folder 4 (Box Box 12)
  - Outstanding Equity proposals, Folder 5 (Box Box 12)
  - LORT negotiation committee, Folder 6 (Box Box 12)
  - William Stewart Correspondence (inter office), Folder 7 (Box Box 12)
  - William Stewart Correspondence (inter office), Folder 8 (Box Box 12)
  - Denize Denize Springer Correspondence Sept. - Dec. 1987, Folder 9 (Box Box 12)
  - Denize Springer Correspondence May - Aug. 1987, Folder 10 (Box Box 12)
  - Denize Springer Correspondence, Jan. - April 1987, Folder 11 (Box Box 12)
  - Denize Springer Correspondence, Folder 12 (Box Box 12)
  - Denize Springer Correspondence, Folder 13 (Box Box 12)
  - William Stewart Correspondence, Folder 14 (Box Box 12)
  - William Stewart Correspondence, Folder 15 (Box Box 12)
  - William Stewart Correspondence, Folder 16 (Box Box 12)
  - William Stewart Correspondence, Folder 17 (Box Box 12)
  - William Stewart Correspondence, Folder 18 (Box Box 12)
  - William Stewart Correspondence, Folder 19 (Box Box 12)
  - William Stewart Correspondence, Folder 20 (Box Box 12)
  - William Stewart Correspondence, Folder 21 (Box Box 12)
  - SSD and C Society of Stage Directors and Choreographers, Folder 22 (Box Box 12)
  - Special Project Committee, Folder 23 (Box Box 12)
  - Script: The Passing of a Queen, O.A. Reardon, Folder 24 (Box Box 12)
  - Statement of Activities and Purposes, Folder 25 (Box Box 12)
  - William Stewart Correspondence (inter office), Folder 26 (Box Box 12)
  - William Stewart Correspondence (inter office), Folder 27 (Box Box 12)
  - William Stewart Correspondence, Jan. - April 1987, Folder 28 (Box Box 12)
  - Correspodence with League of Resident Theatres, Folder 1 (Box Box 13)
  - William Stewart correspondence (inter office), Folder 2 (Box Box 13)
  - William Stewart correspondence (inter office), Folder 3 (Box Box 13)
  - William Stewart correspondence (ghost), Folder 4 (Box Box 13)
  - William Stewart correspondence (ghost), Folder 5 (Box Box 13)
  - William Stewart correspondence (ghost) 1987, Folder 6 (Box Box 13)
  - William Stewarts Biography and Misc. files, Folder 7 (Box Box 13)
  - William Stewart correspondence (solicitations), Folder 8 (Box Box 13)
  - William Stewart correcspondence (communications and marketing), Folder 9 (Box Box 13)
  - League of Resident Theatres correspondence Sept. - Dec. 1971, Folder 10 (Box Box 13)
  - League of Resident Theatres Correspondence May - Aug. 1971, Folder 11 (Box Box 13)
  - League of Resident Theatres correspondence Jan. - April 1971, Folder 12 (Box Box 13)
  - League of Resident Theatres Jan. - July 1973, Folder 13 (Box Box 13)
  - League of Resident Theatres correspondence Aug. - Dec. 1973, Folder 14 (Box Box 13)
  - League of Resident Theatres correspondence Sept. - Dec. 1972, Folder 15 (Box Box 13)
  - League of Resident Theates correspondence May - Aug. 1972, Folder 15 (Box Box 13)
  - League of Resident Theatres correspondence Feb. - April 1972, Folder 16 (Box Box 13)
  - League of Resident Theatres correspondence, Folder 1 (Box Box 14)
  - League of Resident Theatres correspondence, 1970, Folder 2 (Box Box 14)
  - League of Resident Theatres correspondence, Folder 3 (Box Box 14)
  - League of Resident Theatres correspondence, 1966, Folder 4 (Box Box 14)
  - Ensemble grant, Folder 5 (Box Box 14)
  - Ensemble grant, Folder 6 (Box Box 14)
  - National Endowment of the Arts National Council, Folder 7 (Box Box 14)
  - NEH Grant DC 20462-87, Folder 8 (Box Box 14)
  - National Endowment for the Arts, Folder 9 (Box Box 14)
  - National Endowment for the arts, Folder 10 (Box Box 14)
  - NEA interarts program, Folder 11 (Box Box 14)
  - Ad hoc Committee on actors, Folder 12 (Box Box 14)
  - NEA - onsite evaluation, Folder 13 (Box Box 14)
  - Challange grant application and instructions, Folder 14 (Box Box 14)
  - NEA Challenge Grant, Folder 15 (Box Box 14)
  - NEA Challenge Grant, Folder 16 (Box Box 14)
  - NEA Challenge grant, Folder 17 (Box Box 14)
  - Ensamble grant 1984, folder 18 (Box Box 14)
  - Ensemble Grant 1984, Folder 19 (Box Box 14)
  - NEA Reauthorization Material, Folder 20 (Box Box 14)
  - NEA Reauthorization Material 1990, Folder 21 (Box Box 14)
  - NEA opera-musical theatre program, Folder 1 (Box Box 15)
  - NEA intern program, Folder 2 (Box Box 15)
  - NEA Director Fellowship Program, Folder 3 (Box Box 15)
  - National Corporate Theatre Fund 1984/1986, Folder 4 (Box Box 15)
  - National Corporate Theatre Fund Jan. - April 1985, Folder 5 (Box Box 15)
  - NEA Opera-Musical Theatre Program, Folder 6 (Box Box 15)
  - NEA Directors Fellowshhip 1981-1982, Folder 7 (Box Box 15)
  - USIA tour Application, Folder 8 (Box Box 15)
  - NEH application materials, Folder 9 (Box Box 15)
  - Stablization Fund NASF, Folder 10 (Box Box 15)
  - Arena humanities Program, Folder 11 (Box Box 15)
  - Arena Humanities Program Quarterly Report, Folder 12 (Box Box 15)
  - NEA Residencies for Playwrights Pogram, Folder 13 (Box Box 15)
  - NEA Large Professional Theatre Companies, Folder 14 (Box Box 15)
  - NEA Large Professional Theatre Companies, Folder 15 (Box Box 15)
  - NEA Large Professional Theatre Companies, Folder 16 (Box Box 15)
  - NEA Theatre Application, Folder 17 (Box Box 15)
  - Jim Nicola - Fees Jan. 1988, Folder 18 (Box Box 15)
  - National Corporate Theatre Fund May-Nov. 1985, Folder 19 (Box Box 15)
  - NEH - Park SVCS, Folder 20 (Box Box 15)
  - Arena Stage - Fellows Program 1982, Folder 21 (Box Box 15)
  - NEH financial documents, Folder 22 (Box Box 15)
  - Q and A post show discussions: 1985 - 1986 Season:, Folder 23 (Box Box 15)
  - National Theatre Corporate Theatre Fund, Board of Directors meeting minutes, Folder 1 (Box Box 16)
  - NCTF vender location guide, Folder 2 (Box Box 16)
  - NCTF - Draft Plan of Action: Purpose and Goals, Folder 3 (Box Box 16)
  - NCTF "The Real Thing", Folder 4 (Box Box 16)
  - NCTF: additions to the roster, Folder 5 (Box Box 16)
  - NCTF - Planning Committees, Sub-Committe meeting, Folder 6 (Box Box 16)
  - NCTF questionnaire for NCTF Aid to Education fund, Folder 7 (Box Box 16)
  - NCTF Financial Statement june 1983-1984, Folder 8 (Box Box 16)
  - NEA: living stage grant, Folder 9 (Box Box 16)
  - NEA: Large Professional theatre Companies grant application, Folder 10 (Box Box 16)
  - Arena's budget 1980 - 1981, Folder 11 (Box Box 16)
  - NEA Theatre program 5 year plan 1983, Folder 12 (Box Box 16)
  - NEA Theatre application, Folder 13 (Box Box 16)
  - NCTF fund raising status and balances, Folder 14 (Box Box 16)
  - NCTF Planning Committee and Board Meeting, Folder 15 (Box Box 16)
  - NCTF Board members and employees, Folder 16 (Box Box 16)
  - NCTF News and memorandum 1983, Folder 17 (Box Box 16)
  - NCTF News and memorandum, Folder 18 (Box Box 16)
  - NCTF Theatre Fund Fiscal Report July - June 1983, Folder 19 (Box Box 16)
  - NCTF Actors Theatre of Louisville, Folder 20 (Box Box 16)
  - NCTF Board of Directors minutes on meetings 1983, Folder 21 (Box Box 16)
  - American Arts Alliance, Folder 22 (Box Box 16)
  - American Arts Alliance action alert and directors notes, Folder 23 (Box Box 16)
  - American Arts Alliance information memo, Folder 24 (Box Box 16)
  - Alley Theatre - Brown Firing, Folder 25 (Box Box 16)
  - Arena Enterprises Lincense 1950's and 1960's, Folder 26 (Box Box 16)
  - Handicapped Blg. improvements, Folder 27 (Box Box 16)
  - Air Conditioning Carrier 1971, Folder 28 (Box Box 16)
  - Administrative Staff meeting minutes, Folder 1 (Box Box 17)
  - "Auction" 1974-1978, Folder 2 (Box Box 17)
  - Audience Surveys, Folder 3 (Box Box 17)
  - American Arts Alliance material, Folder 4 (Box Box 17)
  - material from the National Arts and the Handicapped Information Service, Folder 5 (Box Box 17)
  - Polysonics acoustical survey and analysis Sept. 1982, Folder 6 (Box Box 17)
  - Board of trustees meeting material, Folder 7 (Box Box 17)
  - Board of Trustees 1983-1985, Folder 8 (Box Box 17)
  - Board list 1983-1987, Folder 9 (Box Box 17)
  - Board of trustees, Folder 10 (Box Box 17)
  - Gift of land: Bernstein, Folder 11 (Box Box 17)
  - Hispanic Language consultant, Folder 12 (Box Box 17)
  - Administrative staff meeting minutes, Folder 13 (Box Box 17)
  - Administrative Staff meeting minutes 1987, Folder 14 (Box Box 17)
  - Administrative Staff meeting minutes 1986, Folder 15 (Box Box 17)
  - Donaldson, Luffkin and Jenrette Cable Television report 1981, Folder 1 (Box Box 18)
  - Theatre Communications Group Inc.report: cable television and the performing arts, 1981, Folder 2 (Box Box 18)
  - 1st County Cable and the Arts, Folder 3 (Box Box 18)
  - minimum basic production contract for off broadway dramatic productions, Folder 4 (Box Box 18)
  - agreements for the Washington Drama Society "The Producer", Folder 5 (Box Box 18)
  - Phonic Ear, Folder 6 (Box Box 18)
  - American Arts, September, 1980, Folder 7 (Box Box 18)
  - audio/visual communications, Folder 8 (Box Box 18)
  - "Will Cable Save the Arts?, Folder 9 (Box Box 18)
  - Arena Sound Status, Folder 10 (Box Box 18)
  - P.B.S. memorandum cable grand alliance report, Folder 11 (Box Box 18)
  - Cable TV and the Arts, Folder 12 (Box Box 18)
  - Producer/Author agreement forms, Folder 13 (Box Box 18)
  - building construction manuel for Arena Stage, Bound Book (Box Box 19)
  - Air Conditioning Manuel of the Arena Stage, Bound Book (Box Box 19)
  - Construction plans, Folder 1 (Box Box 19)
  - Interior Design, Folder 2 (Box Box 19)
  - Bank Statements, Folder 3 (Box Box 19)
  - Metropolitan Electric, Folder 4 (Box Box 19)
  - Lease with RLA (1 of 2), Folder 5 (Box Box 19)